A Guide to the Trust for Mutual Understanding records FA412
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1970, 1975, 1978, 1982, 1987-2012; 3; 45.95 Cubic Feet 121 letter document boxes
  - Soundscape, DF-0426, 2003-2005 (Box 121, Folder 1329)
  - Soundscape, DF-0426, Soundscape, Photos (Box 121, Folder 1329)
  - Soundscape, B-0771, 2005-2009 (Box 121, Folder 1330)
  - Soundscape, DF-0706, 2005-2007, 2009 (Box 121, Folder 1331)
  - Southwest Research and Information Center, B-0645, 2005-2008 (Box 121, Folder 1332)
  - Southwest Research and Information Center, B-0745, 2007-2008 (Box 121, Folder 1333)
  - Southwest Research and Information Center, B-0845, 2007-2008 (Box 121, Folder 1334)
  - Species Survival Network, DF-0545, 2005-2007 (Box 121, Folder 1335)
  - Species Survival Network, DF-0545, Species Survival Network, Summit, Budapest, Hungary, 2006 April (Box 121, Folder 1335)
  - Spoleto Festival USA, B-0368, 2002-2004 (Box 121, Folder 1336)
  - Stanislavsky Theater Studio, DF-0530, 2005-2006 (Box 122, Folder 1337)
  - Stanislavsky Theater Studio, DF-0530, Stanislavsky Theater Studio, STS Volkov Festival, Photos (Box 122, Folder 1337)
  - Stephen Petronio Company, DF-0320, 2000-2004, 2007 (Box 122, Folder 1338)
  - Storefront for Art and Architecture, DF-0715, 2007, 2009 (Box 122, Folder 1339)
  - Sundance Institute, B-0139, 2001-2002 (Box 122, Folder 1340)
  - Sundance Institute, Theater Program, DF-0214, 2000-2002 (Box 122, Folder 1341)
  - Sundance Institute, EC-0413, 2004-2006 (Box 122, Folder 1342)
  - SUSHI Performance and Visual Art, DF-0831, 2007-2008 (Box 122, Folder 1343)
  - Tahoe-Baikal Institute, B-0114, 2000-2003 (Box 122, Folder 1344)
  - Tahoe-Baikal Institute, B-0269, 2001-2003, 2007 (Box 122, Folder 1345)
  - Tahoe-Baikal Institute, EC-0316, 2002-2004 (Box 122, Folder 1346)
  - Tahoe-Baikal Institute, EC-0316, Tahoe-Baikal Institute, 2003 (Box 122, Folder 1346)
  - Tahoe-Baikal Institute, B-0443, 2004-2006 (Box 123, Folder 1347)
  - Tahoe-Baikal Institute, EC-0508, 2005-2006 (Box 123, Folder 1348)
  - Tahoe-Baikal Institute, EC-0508, TBI Photos for TMU, 2005 (Box 123, Folder 1348)
  - Tahoe-Baikal Institute, B-0646, 2006-2008 (Box 123, Folder 1349)
  - Tahoe-Baikal Institute, B-0646, TMU Photos from TBI, 2006 (Box 123, Folder 1349)
  - Tahoe-Baikal Institute, B-0746, 2007-2008 (Box 123, Folder 1350)
  - Tahoe-Baikal Institute, B-0746, Photos from TBI, 2007 (Box 123, Folder 1350)
  - Tahoe-Baikal Institute, B-0846, 2007-2008 (Box 123, Folder 1351)
  - Tahoe-Baikal Institute, B-0846, Photos for TMU, TBI SEE, 2008 (Box 123, Folder 1351)
  - Tahoe-Baikal Institute, Miscellaneous, B-0953, 2006-2008 (Box 123, Folder 1353)
  - Tamarind Institute, B-0140, 2000-2003 (Box 123, Folder 1354)
  - Tamarind Institute, B-0326, 2002-2005 (Box 123, Folder 1354)
  - Tamarind Institute, B-0326, Re-Connection, Panel Discussion Images, Working Images (Box 123, Folder 1354)
  - Tamarind Institute, B-0469, 2004-2008 (Box 123, Folder 1356)
  - The Tank, DF-0748, 2007-2008 (Box 123, Folder 1356)
  - The Tank, DF-0748, Blip Festival Overview (Box 123, Folder 1356)
  - The Tank, DF-0825, 2008-2009 (Box 123, Folder 1357)
  - Theater by the Blind, DF-0130, 1999-2002 (Box 124, Folder 1358)
  - Theatre Communications Group (TCG), TCG/ITI Travel Grants, EC-0211 EC-0300, 2001-2004, 2007 (Box 124, Folder 1359)
  - Theatre Communications Group (TCG), B-0504, B-0601, 2003-2008 (Box 124, Folder 1360)
  - Theatre Communications Group (TCG), B-0504, B-0601, Pics for TCG-ITI Travel Grant for Jo ANna Sherman, Bond St. Theatre, PABP Mostar, 2006 (Box 124, Folder 1360)
  - Theatre Communications Group (TCG), B-0709, B-0801, 2006-2009 (Box 124, Folder 1361)
  - Theatre Communications Group (TCG), Miscellaneous, B-0801, 2008 (Box 124, Folder 1362)
  - Theatre Communications Group (TCG), Miscellaneous, B-0801, Theatre Communications Group, Talking Band; Upstream; James Clotfelter (Box 124, Folder 1362)
  - Theatre Communications Group (TCG), DF-0812, 2008 (Box 124, Folder 1363)
  - Theatre Communications Group, Miscellaneous, DF-0812, 2007-2008 (Box 124, Folder 1364)
  - Theatre of Yugen, B-0873, 2003-2005, 2007-2009 (Box 124, Folder 1365)
  - Theatre of Yugen, Miscellaneous, B-0873, 2005-2007 (Box 124, Folder 1366)
  - ThingsezIsee'm, DF-0317, 2003, 2007-2009 (Box 124, Folder 1367)
  - Thunder Bay Ensemble, B-0296, 2002-2004 (Box 124, Folder 1368)
  - Thunder Bay Ensemble, B-0427, 2003-2005, 2007 (Box 124, Folder 1369)
  - Thunder Bay Ensemble, B-0427, Thunder Bay Ensemble, Time and Shadow Images, Artus, Toaca, 2007 January 15 (Box 124, Folder 1369)
  - Thunder Bay Collaborative, B-0735, 2006-2008 (Box 125, Folder 1370)
  - Thunder Bay Collaborative, B-0735, The Time and Shadow Project, Triple Shadow (USA), Artis (Hungary), Toaca (Romania), 2006 March-2007 October (Box 125, Folder 1370)
  - Thunder Bay Collaborative, B-0735, The Santa Fe Art Institute, Video: Thunderbay Collab with Artus and Toaca, Triple Shadow, 2007 (Box 125, Folder 1370)
  - Thunder Bay Collaborative, B-0735, Thunder Bay Collaborative, Time/Lights/Shadows at SFAI (Box 125, Folder 1370)
  - Tibetan Buddhist Resource Center, DF-0405, 2004-2005 (Box 125, Folder 1371)
  - Tickle the Sleeping Giant, B-0831, 2006-2008 (Box 125, Folder 1372)
  - Tonal Motion, DF-0541, 2005-2006, 2008 (Box 125, Folder 1373)
  - Tonal Motion, B-0726, 2006-2007, 2009 (Box 125, Folder 1374)
  - TOVA, EC-0312, 2002-2003 (Box 125, Folder 1375)
  - The Toynbee Prize Foundation, B-0256, 2002-2003, 2007 (Box 125, Folder 1376)
  - The Tributary Fund, B-0847, 2007-2009 (Box 125, Folder 1378)
  - Tricklock Company, DF-0342, 2003-2004, 2007 (Box 125, Folder 1378)
  - Tricklock, B-0428, 2003-2006 (Box 125, Folder 1379)
  - Tricklock Company, B-0428, Tricklock, Akhe Russian Engineering Theatre, Photos from Revolution International Theatre Festival, 2004 (Box 125, Folder 1379)
  - Tulane University, Preservation of the Architectural Heritage of the Russian North, DF-0131, 1998-2002, 2007 (Box 125, Folder 1380)
  - Tvistomi, DF-0727, 2007, 2009 (Box 125, Folder 1381)
  - Tvistomi, Miscellaneous, DF-0727, 2008 (Box 125, Folder 1381A)
  - Umbau School of Architecture, DF-0809, 2007-2010 (Box 125, Folder 1382)
  - Umbau School of Architecture, DF-0809, Travnik Chapter, Umbau, 2008 (Box 125, Folder 1382)
  - Umbau School of Architecture, DF-0809, Photography, Umbau, 2008 (Box 125, Folder 1382)
  - Unique Projects, Inc., DF-0523, 2001-2005 (Box 126, Folder 1383)
  - Unique Projects, Inc., B-0633, 2003-2006, 2008 (Box 126, Folder 1384)
  - Unique Projects, Inc., DF-0749, 2007-2008 (Box 126, Folder 1385)
  - United Nations Foundation, EC-0801 (Reallocation of RFF, B-0676), 2006-2008 (Box 126, Folder 1386)
  - Resources for the Future, B-0676, 2006
  - Resources for the Future, B-0676, 2007
  - United States-Central and Eastern European Environment Foundation, DF-0335, 2003-2004 (Box 126, Folder 1387)
  - University of California, Berkeley, Cal Performances, B-0327, 2003-2004 (Box 126, Folder 1388)
  - University of California, Berkeley Art Museum & Pacific Film Archive, DF-0306, 2001-2004 (Box 126, Folder 1389)
  - University of California: School of Theater, Film, and Television, B-0833, 2007-2009 (Box 126, Folder 1390)
  - University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), School of Theater, Film, and Television, EC-0506, 2004-2005, 2007 (Box 126, Folder 1391)
  - University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), School of Theater, Film, and Television, B-0634, 2005-2009 (Box 126, Folder 1392)
  - University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), Michael Hackett, B-0430, 1992, 1997, 2001-2005 (Box 127, Folder 1393)
  - University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), Michael Hackett, B-0430, UCLA, Meditation on Virginity, Photos (Box 127, Folder 1393)
  - UCLA Live, B-0874, 2005, 2007-2010 (Box 127, Folder 1394)
  - UCLA Live, Miscellaneous, B-0874, 2008-2010 (Box 127, Folder 1395)
  - University of Chicago, Department of Slavic Languages and Literature, DF-0343, 2003-2004, 2007 (Box 127, Folder 1396)
  - University of Connecticut, DF-0627, 2005-2008 (Box 127, Folder 1397)
  - University of Illinois at Chicago, Shadow Theater of Moscow, B-0257, 2002-2003 (Box 127, Folder 1398)
  - University of Iowa, International Writing Program, B-01105, 2001-2003, 2007 (Box 127, Folder 1399)
  - University of Iowa, International Writing Program, EC-0328, 2003-2006 (Box 127, Folder 1400)
  - University of Maryland, Department of Art History and Archaeology, DF-0300 (Cancelled), 2000-2002, 2007 (Box 127, Folder 1401)
  - University of Michigan, International Institute, B-0297, 2002-2004 (Box 127, Folder 1402)
  - University of Montana, Kamchatka Steelhead Project with Wild Salmon Center, B-0176, 2000-2002, 2007 (Box 128, Folder 1403)
  - University of Montana, B-0270, 2000, 2002-2003, 2007 (Box 128, Folder 1404)
  - University of the Pacific, DF-0728, 2006-2010 (Box 128, Folder 1405)
  - University of the Pacific, DF-0728, Polish Images TMU Keith Hartschloek and Quicktime Video, Brubeck in Poland (Box 128, Folder 1405)
  - University of Pittsburgh, DF-0750, 2007-2008 (Box 128, Folder 1406)
  - University of Pittsburgh, DF-0750, University of Pittsburgh, Photos 2008 Activities (Box 128, Folder 1406)
  - University of Tennessee, Knoxville, DF-0441, 2004-2005 (Box 128, Folder 1407)
  - University of Tennessee, Knoxville, Miscellaneous, DF-0441, 2005 (Box 128, Folder 1408)
  - University of Toledo, DF-0442, 2003-2006 (Box 128, Folder 1409)
  - University of Toledo, DF-0442, University of Toledo (Box 128, Folder 1409)
  - University of Toledo, Miscellaneous, DF-0442, 1993-1995, 1997, 2001-2004 (Box 128, Folder 1410)
  - The University of Vermont, Gund Institute for Ecological Economics, B-0536, 2004-2005, 2008-2009 (Box 129, Folder 1411)
  - The University of Vermont, The Rubenstein School of Environment and Natural Resources, B-0647, 2006, 2008 (Box 129, Folder 1412)
  - UrbanArts Institute, B-0328, 2003, 2005 (Box 129, Folder 1413)
  - UrbanArts Institute, B-0328, Paftalizam Video Documentary of the Unifying Gift, A USA-MK Artistic Collaboration (Box 129, Folder 1413)
  - U.S. Biennial, DF-0832, 2007-2009 (Box 129, Folder 1414)
  - U.S.-Ukraine Foundation, B-0832, 2007-2010 (Box 129, Folder 1415)
  - Vermont Studio Center, B-01106, 2001-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 129, Folder 1416)
  - Vermont Studio Center, DF-0524, 2004-2006, 2008 (Box 129, Folder 1417)
  - Vermont Studio Center, DF-0524, Bartok Maticka @VSC (Box 129, Folder 1417)
  - Voice of Roma, DF-0838, 2008-2009 (Box 129, Folder 1418)
  - WaxFactory, Quartet, B-0161, 2001-2002, 2006-2007 (Box 130, Folder 1419)
  - WaxFactory, B-0258, 2002-2003, 2006-2007 (Box 130, Folder 1420)
  - WaxFactory, B-0329, 2002-2004, 2006-2007 (Box 130, Folder 1421)
  - WaxFactory, B-0329, WaxFactory, Cleansed, 2003 May (Box 130, Folder 1421)
  - WaxFactory, B-0329, WaxFactory, 02 & 03 Grants, 2002-2003 (Box 130, Folder 1421)
  - WaxFactory, B-0431, 2002-2007 (Box 130, Folder 1422)
  - WaxFactory, DF-0400, 2003-2004, 2007 (Box 130, Folder 1423)
  - WaxFactory, B-0525, 2003-2005, 2008-2009 (Box 130, Folder 1424)
  - WaxFactory, B-0525, WaxFactory, Still Photographs from "...She Said...", Work Sample, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 1424)
  - WaxFactory, Miscellaneous, B-0525 (Box 130, Folder 1425)
  - WaxFactory, DF-0500, 2004-2006, 2009 (Box 130, Folder 1426)
  - WaxFactory, Miscellaneous, DF-0500, 2001-2002 (Box 130, Folder 1427)
  - WaxFactory, B-0635, 2005-2009 (Box 130, Folder 1428)
  - WaxFactory, B-0635, WaxFactory, "...She Said..." (Box 130, Folder 1428)
  - WaxFactory, Miscellaneous, B-0635, 2006 (Box 130, Folder 1429)
  - WaxFactory, B-0736, 2004, 2007, 2009 (Box 130, Folder 1430)
  - WaxFactory, B-0835, 2005, 2007-2009 (Box 130, Folder 1431)
  - WaxFactory, Miscellaneous, B-0835, 2008 (Box 130, Folder 1432)
  - Western Folklife Center, DF-0121, 2000-2003 (Box 131, Folder 1433)
  - Western Folklife Center, B-0298, 2002-2004 (Box 131, Folder 1434)
  - Western Folklife Center, B-0471, 2004-2006 (Box 131, Folder 1435)
  - Western Folklife Center, B-0471, Western Folklife Center, Mongolia Cultural Exchange, Audio (Box 131, Folder 1435)
  - Western Folklife Center, B-0471, Western Folklife Center, Mongolia Cultural Exchange, Photos (Box 131, Folder 1435)
  - The Wild Foundation, B-0449, 2003-2005, 2007 (Box 131, Folder 1436)
  - The Wild Foundation, EC-0405, 2003-2005, 2007 (Box 131, Folder 1437)
  - The Wild Foundation, B-0537, 2005, 2007 (Box 131, Folder 1438)
  - The Wild Salmon Center, B-0271, 2002-2004 (Box 131, Folder 1439)
  - The Wild Salmon Center, B-0271, Wild Salmon Center Slides (Box 131, Folder 1439)
  - The Wild Salmon Center, Recreational Fisheries, B-0339, 2002-2004 (Box 131, Folder 1440)
  - The Wild Salmon Center, B-0444, 2003-2006 (Box 131, Folder 1441)
  - The Wild Salmon Center, B-0538, 2005-2007 (Box 131, Folder 1442)
  - The Wild Salmon Center, B-0677, 2006-2008 (Box 132, Folder 1443)
  - The Wild Salmon Center, B-0781, 2007-2008 (Box 132, Folder 1444)
  - The Wild Salmon Center, B-0848, 2007-2009 (Box 132, Folder 1445)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), Siberian Tiger Response Team, B-0177, 2001-2003 (Box 132, Folder 1446)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), Siberian Tiger Response Team, Miscellaneous, B-0177, 1998, 2000-2001 (Box 132, Folder 1447)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), Sakhalin Sturgeon, B-0340, 2003-2005, 2009 (Box 132, Folder 1448)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), Sakhalin Sturgeon, B-0340, WCS Final Report, Sakhalin Sturgeon Project (Box 132, Folder 1448)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), Wildlife Project Russia Far East (RFE), B-0341, 2003-2004 (Box 132, Folder 1449)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), Veterinary Response Teams, B-0376, 2003-2005 (Box 132, Folder 1450)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), Brown Bear Management, B-0377, 2003-2004, 2007-2008 (Box 132, Folder 1451)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), Siberian Tiger, B-0452, 2004-2005, 2007 (Box 132, Folder 1452)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), Empowering Local Communities, B-0470, 2004-2005, 2007 (Box 132, Folder 1453)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), "Bear Necessities", B-0539, 2005-2007 (Box 132, Folder 1454)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), Tsaatan Workshop, B-0542, 2005-2209 (Box 133, Folder 1455)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), Sturgeon, B-0648, 2006-2009 (Box 133, Folder 1456)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), Mongolian Saiga Conservation, B-0678, 2006-2009 (Box 133, Folder 1457)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), Tiger-Human Conflict Resolution, B-0747, 2005, 2007-2009 (Box 133, Folder 1458)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), Tiger-Human Conflict Resolution, B-0747, WCS Russia Vet Training, Workshop, 2007 November-December (Box 133, Folder 1458)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), B-0849, 2007-2011 (Box 133, Folder 1459)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), B-0864, 2007-2009 (Box 133, Folder 1460)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society, Miscellaneous, B-0864, 2008 (Box 133, Folder 1461)
  - Williamstown Art Conservation Center, B-0224, 2002-2003 (Box 133, Folder 1462)
  - Williamstown Art Conservation Center, EC-0409, 2002, 2004-2005 (Box 134, Folder 1463)
  - Williamstown Art Conservation Center, EC-0509, 2005-2006 (Box 134, Folder 1464)
  - Williamstown Art Conservation Center, B-0636, 2004-2007 (Box 134, Folder 1465)
  - Williamstown Art Conservation Center, B-0737, 2006-2008 (Box 134, Folder 1466)
  - Williamstown Art Conservation Center, EC-0707, 2006-2008 (Box 134, Folder 1467)
  - Williamstown Art Conservation Center, EC-0707, Williamstown Art Conservation Center, 2007 Projects, Exploratory Exchange, Mongolia, Interpretive Planning, Bulgaria (Box 134, Folder 1467)
  - Williamstown Art Conservation Lab, B-0836, 2007-2008, 2010 (Box 134, Folder 1468)
  - Williamstown Art Conservation Center, B-0875, 2008-2009 (Box 134, Folder 1469)
  - Winrock International, EC-0324, 2003-2004, 2007-2008 (Box 134, Folder 1470)
  - Women Make Movies, DF-0115, 1994-1996, 2000-2003 (Box 134, Folder 1471)
  - Woods Hole Research Center, B-01109, B-0201, 2001-2004 (Box 134, Folder 1472)
  - Woods Hole Research Center, B-0350, 2003-2005, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 1473)
  - Woods Hole Research Center, EC-0514, 2005-200\8 (Box 135, Folder 1474)
  - Woods Hole Research Center, B-0748, 2007-2009 (Box 135, Folder 1475)
  - The Wooster Group, EC-0614, 2006-2007 (Box 135, Folder 1476)
  - The Wooster Group, B-0837, 2001, 2008-2009 (Box 135, Folder 1477)
  - World Archaeological Congress, B-0299, 2002-2004 (Box 135, Folder 1478)
  - World Monuments Fund, Mildred Schmertz Poland Trip, DF-0219, 2002-2003, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 1479)
  - World Monuments Fund, DF-0232, 2001-2003, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 1480)
  - World Music Institute, B-0141, 1999-2002 (Box 135, Folder 1481)
  - World Music Institute, B-0259, 2000-2003, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 1481)
  - World Music Institute, EC-0203, 2002, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 1482)
  - World Music Institute, B-0569, 1999, 2004-2007 (Box 136, Folder 1483)
  - World Music Institute, B-0876, 2007-2010 (Box 136, Folder 1484)
  - World Resources Institute, B-01114, 2001-2003 (Box 136, Folder 1485)
  - World Resources Institute, DF-0446, 2004-2008 (Box 136, Folder 1486)
  - World Resources Institute, EC-0609, 2006-2007 (Box 136, Folder 1487)
  - World Resources Institute, EC-0805, 2007-2008, 2010 (Box 136, Folder 1488)
  - World Wildlife Fund (WWF), Bering Sea Educational Exchange, B-0178, 2000-2003 (Box 136, Folder 1489)
  - World Wildlife Fund (WWF), Bering Sea Educational Exchange, B-0178, WWF "Treasurers of the Bering Sea" Program Photos, 2003 October 10-17 (Box 136, Folder 1489)
  - World Wildlife Fund (WWF), Bering Sea Educational Exchange, B-0178, WWF, Alaska Public Radio Network Story on WWF's "Treasurers Across the Bering Sea", 2003 October (Box 136, Folder 1489)
  - World Wildlife Fund (WWF), EC-0329, 2003-2006 (Box 136, Folder 1490)
  - World Wildlife Fund (WWF), B-0649, 2005-2009 (Box 136, Folder 1491)
  - World Wildlife Fund (WWF), B-0679, 2006-2008 (Box 137, Folder 1492)
  - World Wildlife Fund (WWF), Miscellaneous, B-0679, 2001-2002 (Box 137, Folder 1493)
  - World Wildlife Fund (WWF), B-0850, 2007-2010 (Box 137, Folder 1494)
  - World Wildlife Fund (WWF), B-0850, WWF Photos, Polar Bear Exchange, 2010 March (Box 137, Folder 1494)
  - Yale University, School of Drama, B-0330, 2002-2004 (Box 137, Folder 1496)
  - Yale University, School of Drama, Miscellaneous, B-0330, 1998, 2001, 2005 (Box 137, Folder 1496)
  - Yale University, School of Drama, B-0738, 2006-2008 (Box 137, Folder 1498)
  - Yale University, School of Drama, Miscellaneous, B-0738, 2006 (Box 137, Folder 1498)
  - Yale University, School of Drama, B-0772, 2006-2008 (Box 137, Folder 1499)
  - Yale University, School of Drama, B-0772, Yale Repertory Theatre, Supplementary Video for Farm in the Cave/TMU Application (Box 137, Folder 1499)
  - Yale University, School of Drama, B-0772, Yale Repertory Theatre, Supplementary Information for Farm in the Cave, Photos (Box 137, Folder 1499)
  - Yale University, School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, B-0445, 2003-2007 (Box 137, Folder 1500)
  - Yale University, School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, B-0749, 2007-2009 (Box 137, Folder 1501)
  - Yara Arts Group, Circle, B-0612, 2000-2003 (Box 138, Folder 1502)
  - Yara Arts Group, EC-0330, 2003-2004, 2006 (Box 138, Folder 1503)
  - Yara Arts Group, DF-0443, 2004-2005 (Box 138, Folder 1504)
  - Yara Arts Group, DF-0443, Yara Arts Group, Photos of Koliada, 2005 (Box 138, Folder 1504)
  - Yara Arts Group, B-0838, 2001, 2004, 2007-2009 (Box 138, Folder 1505)
  - Yerba Buena Center for the Arts, B-0739, 1991, 1995, 2006-2009 (Box 138, Folder 1506)
  - Zeitgeist, DF-0707, 2004-2007, 2009 (Box 138, Folder 1507)
  - Zenon Dance Company, B-0331, 2002-2003 (Box 138, Folder 1508)
  - Zenon Dance Company, Miscellaneous, B-0331, 2002 (Box 138, Folder 1509)
  - Zoo District Theatre, B-0260, 1998-2000, 2002-2004 (Box 138, Folder 1510)
  - ZviDance, EC-0313, 1998, 2000-2003, 2007 (Box 138, Folder 1511)
  - ZviDance, Miscellaneous, EC-0313, 2003 (Box 138, Folder 1512)
  - ZviDance, B-0637, 1996, 1998, 2000, 2003-2004, 2006 (Box 138, Folder 1513)
- Trust for Mutual Understanding Annual Reports, 1985-2007; 5; 10 Bound Volumes 10 bound volumes
  Arrangement
  Chronological
  Annual reports
  - Trust for Mutual Understanding Annual Report 1985-2007 (Item REF 303.482 TRU 1985-2007)
  - Trust for Mutual Understanding Annual Report 1998 (Item REF 303.48 TRU 1998)
  - Trust for Mutual Understanding Annual Report 1999 (Item REF 303.482 TRU 1999)
  - Trust for Mutual Understanding Annual Report 2000 (Item REF 303.482 TRU 2000)
  - Trust for Mutual Understanding Annual Report 2002 (Item REF 303.482 TRU 2002)
  - Trust for Mutual Understanding Annual Report 2003 (Item REF 303.482 TRU 2003)
  - Trust for Mutual Understanding Annual Report 2004 (Item REF 303.482 TRU 2004)
  - Trust for Mutual Understanding Annual Report 2005 (Item REF 303.482 TRU 2005)
  - Trust for Mutual Understanding Annual Report 2006 (Item REF 303.482 TRU 2006)
  - Trust for Mutual Understanding Annual Report 2007 (Item REF 303.482 TRU 2007)